Guide to the League of Women Voters of Montana records 1921-1989
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- League of Women Voters of Great Falls
  - Miscellany
    - Agendas; "concensus" forms re local League's position on various issues; studies (re water, sewage disposal, institutions, schools, energy, local government, voter service, etc.), 1960-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 17 / 8)
    - Programs; promotional materials, 1963-1986 (Box-folder 17 / 9)
  - Clippings
    - re Great Falls League, 1955-1986 (Box-folder 17 / 10)
- League of Women Voters of Havre
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 17 / 11)
  - Financial Records
    - Budgets; financial reports; audit reports; pledges; finance drives, 1955-1976 (Box-folder 17 / 12)
  - Minutes
    - General League meetings; Board meetings, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 17 / 13-14)
  - Organization
    - Membership and officer lists; bylaws, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 18 / 1)
  - Printed Material
    - List of printed materials separated to the Library (Box-folder 18 / 2)
  - Reports
    - Annual reports (includes recommendations to National League), 1958-1975 (Box-folder 18 / 3)
  - Miscellany
    - Agendas; "concensus" forms re local League's position on various issues; studies (re state and local government, campaign finances, voters service, libraries, institutions, water, city recreation, etc.), 1968-1975 (Box-folder 18 / 4)
    - Programs; brochures; etc., 1965-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 18 / 5)
  - Clippings
    - re Havre League, 1956-1973 (Box-folder 18 / 6)
- League of Women Voters of Helena
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous, 1954-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 18 / 7-8)
  - Financial Records
    - Budgets; financial reports; expenditures, 1952-1988 (Box-folder 18 / 9)
  - Minutes
    - General League meetings; Board meetings, 1952-1982, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 18 / 10-12)
  - Organization
    - Membership and officers lists; bylaws; application for local League status; duties of Board, 1952-1988 (Box-folder 19 / 1)
  - Printed Material
    - Helena Voter and Voter, newsletters of Helena League (scattered), 1978-1994 (Box-folder 19 / 2)
    - Capital City Bulletin, newsletter of Helena League, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 19 / 2a)
    - Capital Report, legislative newsletters of Helena League (scattered issues), 1979-1989 (Box-folder 19 / 3)
    - List of printed material separated to Library (Box-folder 19 / 4)
  - Reports
    - Annual reports (includes recommentations to National League), 1958-1981 (Box-folder 19 / 5-6)
  - Miscellany
    - Agendas; "concensus" forms re local League's position on various issues; studies (re local government, recreation, sanitation, child care, library services, natural resources, housing, finance drive, education, voters service, taxation, state government, water, zoning, etc.), 1955-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 19 / 7-8)
    - History of the League; programs; brochures, 1961-1980, n.d. (Box-folder 19 / 9)
  - Clippings
    - re Helena League, 1957-1988 (Box-folder 19 / 10)
- League of Women Voters of Liberty County
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 19 / 11)
  - Minutes
    - Board meeting, Jan. 5, 1978 (Box-folder 19 / 12)
  - Organization
    - Membership and officer lists; bylaws; application for Provisional League status, 1972-1987 (Box-folder 19 / 13)
  - Printed Material
    - List of printed material separated to Library (Box-folder 19 / 14)
  - Reports
    - Annual reports (includes recommendations to National League), 1972-1981 (Box-folder 19 / 15)
  - Miscellany
    - Agendas; "concensus" forms re local Leagues position on various issues; studies (re local government, etc.) (Box-folder 19 / 16)
  - Clippings
    - re Liberty County League, 1976 (Box-folder 19 / 17)
- League of Women Voters of Missoula
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 19 / 18)
  - Financial Records
    - Budgets; financial reports, 1955-1976 (Box-folder 20 / 1)
  - Minutes
    - General League meetings; Board meetings, 1955-1983 (Box-folder 20 / 2-5)
  - Organization
    - Membership and officer lists; bylaws; unit organization, 1951-1987 (Box-folder 20 / 6)
  - Printed Material
    - Voter, newsletters of Missoula League, Sept.1991- Feb. 1992 (Box-folder 20 / 7)
    - List of printed materials separated to the Library (Box-folder 20 / 8)
  - Reports
    - Annual reports (includes recommendations to National League), 1955, 1959-1981 (Box-folder 20 / 9-10)
  - Miscellany
    - Agendas; "concensus" forms re local League's position on various issues; studies (re city-county government, education, sanitation, voters service, library, hunger, water, Indians, etc.), 1955-1987 (Box-folder 21 / 1-2)
    - History of the League; handbook for members; summary of activities; brochures, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 21 / 3)
  - Clippings
    - re Missoula League, 1954-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 21 / 4)
- League of Women Voters of Ravalli County
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous, 1969-1988 (Box-folder 21 / 5)
  - Financial Records
    - Budgets; financial reports, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 21 / 6)
  - Minutes
    - General League meetings; Board meetings, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 21 / 7)
  - Organization
    - Membership and officer lists; bylaws; application for Provisional League status, 1969-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 21 / 8)
  - Printed Material
    - List of printed materials separated to Library (Box-folder 21 / 9)
  - Reports
    - Annual reports (includes recommendations to National League), 1970-1981 (Box-folder 21 / 10)
  - Miscellany
    - Agendas; "concensu" forms re local League's position on various issues; studies (re local government, floodplain, land use, water supply, voters service, job corps, etc.), 1970-1980 (Box-folder 21 / 11)
  - Clippings
    - re Ravalli County League, 1972, 1976 (Box-folder 21 / 12)
- League of Women Voters of South Lincoln County
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 21 / 13)
  - Minutes
    - General League meetings; Board meetings, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 21 / 14)
  - Organization
    - Membership and officer lists; bylaws; application for Provisional League status, 1976-1977, n.d. (Box-folder 21 / 15)
  - Printed Material
    - List of printed material separated to Library (Box-folder 21 / 16)
  - Reports
    - Annual reports, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 21 / 17)
  - Miscellany
    - Agendas; studies (re analysis of Troy and Libby, land use, coal tax, etc.), 1978-1986 (Box-folder 21 / 18)
    - Calendar of events; media list, 1978 (Box-folder 21 / 19)
  - Clippings
    - re South Lincoln County Provisional League, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 21 / 20)